DYNAMITE KISS
EPISODE 12
Look at it. I'm fine.
-What are we going to do about your wrist?
-Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
It's okay. No one got hurt.
Why are you crying?
I'm sorry.
My goodness.
After the divorce, my ex-husband
stopped paying for child support.
I needed a proper job,
so I applied to Natural BeBe.
Was it to the Mother TF Team?
Yes.
I was an assistant manager
at another baby product company,
so I had high hopes,
but my application didn't pass.
I was devastated.
I felt utterly useless.
That's not true.
I think I took out my anger about my life
on Natural BeBe.
I posted malicious comments
on online mom communities
and called customer service
to curse out the representatives
and make issues out of nothing.
I'll gladly accept
any punishment you see fit.
I'll also post on the online communities
and come clean about what I did
and explain that it was all fabricated.
I'm really sorry.
Gosh, I'm hungry.
What should we eat for dinner?
Sushi?
Or pasta?
Fried chicken?
I'm fine. I'm not really hungry.
You don't seem to be in a good mood.
Da-rim.
Everything worked out.
It's done.
Okay?
I probably took
Ms. Lee So-yeong's spot, right?
If I didn't lie to get hired,
she would've been on the team.
You're reading too much into it.
Even if it wasn't her,
I'm sure
someone more qualified
would've gotten my spot.
And that someone
could've been in a more urgent
and desperate situation than me.
It makes me question
the choices I've made.
Well done, everyone.
-Good job, everyone!
-We're done.
-It's over now, Da-rim.
-Team dinner tonight?
How about a refreshing beer?
-That sounds so nice.
-Excellent idea.
-Right, Mr. Kang?
-What should we eat?
-Grilled intestines.
-Ms. Go Da-rim.
How's your injury?
It's healing.
Is that so?
CERTIFICATE OF MARRIAGE STATUS
NAME: GO DA-RIM
STATUS: UNMARRIED
Is this real?
Yeah.
That woman
-was never married.
-What?
CERTIFICATE OF MARRIAGE STATUS
NAME: KIM SEON-U, STATUS: DIVORCED
NAME: GO DA-RIM, STATUS: UNMARRIED
Are you saying she lied to get a job?
You shouldn't be angry at her.
You should actually be thankful.
Why would I?
She created an opportunity.
An opportunity
to completely crush Gong Ji-hyeok.
CERTIFICATE OF MARRIAGE STATUS
You must've been so upset.
The company should've taken
better preventive measures.
It's okay, ma'am.
The company is wholly at fault for this.
Speaking of which,
let me formally request that we establish
clear guidelines for protecting CS staff
and implement mental-health support.
That's a good idea.
We'll work on that.
-Oh my. Thank you, ma'am.
-Thank you.
Also,
we'd like for you
to do a press interview, Ms. Go.
Is that okay with you?
-Pardon?
-You need to clear your name.
I think it'd be even better
if you do it with Mr. Kim Seon-u
as a couple.
You could even talk about
working together.
A press interview?
Does it mean she's going to be on TV?
You'll be famous nationwide.
You have to do it, no matter what.
Then I'll schedule one
as soon as possible.
That might be difficult.
Ms. Lee So-yeong will inevitably come up
during the interview.
If the issue is highlighted again,
she'll come under fire.
She already confessed and apologized.
Do we have any reason
to push her to the brink?
I agree with him.
I think it'd be best not to do it.
Is that so?
All right then.
But let us at least post an announcement
on the company bulletin board.
To highlight your exceptional service.
You'd be okay with that much, right?
Yes.
You were right.
Ji-hyeok knows Go Da-rim
is single.
Well done.
Just keep praising him
and stroking his ego.
The higher he rises…
the more painful it'll be when he falls.
Ms. Go, we saw the announcement
on the company bulletin board.
Congratulations on being
Employee of the Month.
Did you get that injury
while saving the baby?
You're so cool.
Gosh, I'm flattered.
I didn't do anything special.
Ms. Go, our Employee of the Month,
always had a strong moral compass
and acted with sincerity.
Of course.
Ms. Go, our Employee of the Month,
is known for her unwavering
sense of responsibility.
That's right.
Enjoy your lunch.
-Thank you. You too.
-You too.
You're the Employee of the Month's
team leader.
How does it feel?
Well…
It feels nice.
I see.
You know, Da-rim loves beef.
Come on now, Go-eun.
You don't need to say that out loud.
There's no way Mr. Gong would just ignore
such a momentous occasion.
After all, Ms. Go,
our Employee of the Month,
brought such prestige to our team.
Of course. If he's at all grateful,
he can't just ignore it.
-For sure.
You all should know better now.
Mr. Gong would never.
-There's no way.
It's time for a proper team dinner.
Beef.
It'll be my treat.
-Gong Ji-hyeok!
I'll search for a restaurant immediately.
Korean beef.
-Korean beef?
-Yes, please.
Might as well go all out.
-That sounds so nice.
-We might as well if we can.
Let's step out for coffee.
-It'll be my treat.
-Oh my gosh.
That's the Employee of the Month's
assistant manager for you.
You can tell you're a learned man.
Come on, Da-rim.
Sorry, I think I'll pass.
I don't feel too great.
You guys go ahead.
She barely ate her food.
What's going on?
She's turning down free coffee?
This is totally your style, right?
But you always wear stuff like this.
What a pretty color.
You said you had a kid
who goes to daycare, right?
-Yes.
-Great.
Can you suggest an outfit for me?
Something suitable
for a talent show at a daycare.
Pardon? Where?
Gosh, that's so pretty.
-You think so?
-Yeah.
A talent show.
Show?
You're going to a show?
What?
Yeah, I'm going to a friend's show.
I mean, a friend's party.
Right, so what sort of party?
What's the theme?
The theme is
just a gathering of friends.
We'll be singing and dancing.
I guess you can call that the theme.
Okay. You should've asked me.
That's my specialty.
Let's see here.
Oh my.
This one's great.
Well, you see, the guests at the party
will be on the young side.
That might be a bit too much.
They're young?
How young?
Well…
They're a lot younger than I am.
Listen.
Don't be intimidated.
You need to go all out
when you're with a younger crowd.
Can you show us
a few more party dresses like this?
Yes, ma'am.
-Goodbye, Jun.
-Bye, Jun!
Bye.
Jun, your dad should be here soon.
We'll wait with you.
Jun!
Hello.
-Hello.
My goodness, did you wait long?
I'm sorry.
I had to pick up the guitar from a friend.
It's fine.
Let's go home.
Give me your bag.
Why the long face?
What happened?
Did seeing your friends rehearse
make you nervous?
-No.
-Don't worry about a thing.
I'm an excellent guitarist.
I'm sure all your friends
will end up becoming jealous of you.
Let's go and practice.
-Should we?
-Yeah.
Let's go!
NEW SPRING WOODS KINDERGARTEN
Be careful.
All right, all right.
I'll come visit
when Da-rim has some free time.
Don't even get me started.
That company can't run without Da-rim.
She's so busy.
All right, take care.
Bye.
I'm home.
Da-rim.
Come here.
I was just on the phone
with your aunt Myeong-ja,
and she insists we come by to visit.
You know,
for the fresh country air and stuff.
That sounds nice.
It's been a while since I last saw her.
We saw her often when Dad was alive.
We used to have
marsh snail-catching contests.
That's right.
You and your dad always won.
You wouldn't stop
even in the freezing cold.
Who could beat that?
Did I?
You really take after your dad.
He'd be so proud of you.
You're hardworking, tenacious,
and honest, just like him.
Oh, it's time for dinner.
LIVE WITH HONESTY
Dad.
Sorry.
LIVE WITH HONESTY
MOTHER TF TEAM CANDIDATE ASSESSMENT
2025 MOTHER TF TEAM CANDIDATE ASSESSMENT
YANG HUI-SUK, LEE GO-EUN, GO DA-RIM
EVALUATOR: MA JONG-GU
RESULT: PASS
FAIL
MOTHER TF TEAM
GO DA-RIM
I HEREBY SUBMIT MY RESIGNATION AS OF
MAY 21, 2025 DUE TO PERSONAL REASONS
LETTER OF RESIGNATION
I'm on board too.
I think we can trust him
with the development of the new product.
There won't be much
internal pushback either.
He handled the recent
mom-community incident well,
so our public opinion is good too.
Look at how she's backing you up.
I expect you to show proper results.
Enough to silence any board opposition
about you becoming vice president.
Then I'd like to make a request.
What is it?
If this project is a success,
please renew the contracts
of all my team members
as full-time employees.
Why do you keep insisting on
helping those women?
We still have some time
before their internships end, right?
Yes, we do.
But having his team members
become full-time employees
when he gets promoted
might be better overall.
Right.
To complement
the inauguration ceremony, huh?
All right, go ahead.
Yes, sir.
Ji-hyeok.
You can do this, right?
Of course, I can.
I trust my team members
more than I trust myself.
That's why I'm so grateful for you.
-What?
-You hired them yourself.
They're all so talented in their own ways.
You really have a good eye for people.
-Don't mention it.
-Keep it up.
Developing new products
is a core business of our company.
Can we take on such an important task?
Why not?
We've done pretty well for ourselves.
He's right.
There were always
a few obstacles in the way,
but we've always produced good results.
I believe we can do this.
Right, Da-rim?
I'm not sure
if this is the right time
for me to say this,
but I have to tell you--
Before that,
there's one more important announcement.
-An important announcement?
-What is it?
What's more important than this?
If this project succeeds,
I've gotten the approval
to make all of you full-time employees.
-Really?
-Full-time employees?
-Oh my. I can't believe this.
-Full-time employees!
We have Go Da-rim,
the Employee of the Month,
so of course we'll succeed.
Let's do our best, Da-rim.
Everyone, let's all become
full-time employees!
Let's do it!
I can't believe this!
-I'm going to work really hard.
-Where do we begin?
LETTER OF RESIGNATION
Mr. Gong.
I don't think I can continue working here.
I'm sorry.
I won't take this.
I appreciate the concern,
but I've made up my mind.
With my mom out of the hospital,
a couple of part-time jobs
should be enough to make
the interest payments and what I owe you.
It's not about money.
All applicants with notable
academic backgrounds,
experience, and qualifications
were cut
during the application screening stage.
They even chose the ones
with the lowest interview scores.
Me included.
Why did they do that?
From the start,
they weren't looking
to make a proper team.
So everyone was right.
A loser team just for show.
That was true at first.
If I'm being honest,
that's what I thought as well.
Right.
When everyone had given up on this team,
there was one person
who didn't.
Do you know who that is?
It's you, Da-rim.
Are you just going to let people
look down on you?
Without even putting up a fight?
This report
is the result of us running around
and putting our heads together.
For them, this job and this report
are their livelihoods and lifelines.
JANG JIN-HUI, LEE GO-EUN,
GO DA-RIM, BAE NAN-SUK
Da-rim,
you basically made our team.
You didn't steal
someone else's spot.
You led this team to where it is now
and saved it from fading away.
Ms. Bae Nan-suk.
Ms. Jang Jin-hui.
Ms. Lee Go-eun.
Help them become
full-time employees here.
You can resign after that.
All right?
Okay.
Until then,
I'll do my absolute best.
What did I just see?
What's wrong with my eyes?
Am I overworked?
What's wrong with them?
Why are they hugging?
No, this can't be true.
Oh my goodness.
This can't be happening.
Why are they hugging? Why?
I'm serious!
Are you sure you're not mistaken?
I'm not. I saw it with my own two eyes.
With Mr. Gong?
-There's no way.
-I know what I saw.
-They were hugging.
-Then what about Mr. Kim?
-How could she bring him here?
-Spread out!
Do you have a cold?
Do you want something warm to drink?
No, it's fine.
We were just talking about work.
Oh, right.
Mr. Gong suggested
we all attend the baby fair
to brainstorm ideas
for the new product.
Oh, I see. It sounds like
Mr. Gong made sure to only tell you that.
You two seem to have
a lot of conversations.
What?
It just seems like you and Mr. Gong
have become exceptionally close recently.
Does it? I haven't noticed any changes.
Oh, I almost forgot.
Mr. Gong asked if we'd all be down
to go for a team dinner tonight.
Will Mr. Kim be there as well?
No, it's going to be just us.
That's so cold.
Mr. Kim didn't even hesitate
to participate in the campaign
for you and our team.
How could you not invite him?
Forget it.
I won't be joining.
I can't either. I have plans.
I'm going to spend some quality time
with my husband.
Next up is a performance
by the Moon Class,
"Heart, Heart, Mwah."
-Please give us a round of applause!
-Heart, heart, mwah, mwah
-I love you so much, Mommy and Daddy
-I really love you, I really love you
-I don't know why I love you so
-Heart, heart, mwah, mwah
-I love you so much, Mommy and Daddy
Even when I see you over and over
And every day
Heart, mwah
Even when I see you over and over
Hey, Jun!
Jun!
You're so cute. Oh my gosh!
Good job, Jun!
You're the best! You're adorable!
-Let's look over here.
-There, there.
-Just one.
Ji-ho.
Ji-ho, can you look this way?
-Over here. Let's look here.
-There, there.
Next, we'll welcome Kim Jun and his father
to the stage for their performance
of "Island Baby."
Can we please have Jun's father
come to the stage?
Mr. Kim?
I guess he's not here yet.
-The next performers are ready, right?
-Yes.
Jun, let's have the next team go first,
and then you can go after that, okay?
Wait!
I can do it. That's okay, right?
Who are you?
I'm…
Jun's best friend.
You got this.
Let's do it.
When Mom goes to the shade of the island
To pick oysters
The baby stays behind alone
And keeps watch over the house
-The sea sings
-A lullaby
-The baby rests their head on their arm
-And falls asleep
Hello.
-Jun.
-Dad!
My goodness.
Be careful, you're going to hurt yourself.
Dad, why were you late today?
Sorry.
I'm really sorry about today.
But still, I saw you sing up there.
You were incredible.
I would've been in big trouble
if it weren't for the pretty lady.
Thank you.
How did you know about this?
Jun invited me.
Jun and I decided to become best friends.
Bang!
THANK YOU FOR HAVING ME, DAD
It's hot.
Thank you.
You have such a lovely home.
Thank you
for standing in for me today
at Jun's performance.
I think Jun had a lot of fun,
thanks to you.
Right? Jun and I were in perfect sync.
But…
please don't do this again.
Sorry?
You and I
will have no reason
to see each other after this exhibition.
But Jun is still a kid.
He won't understand
why he can't see you anymore,
and he could get hurt.
Then we can just continue
to see each other.
I already told you.
I like you and Jun.
I have no interest in you as a woman.
So,
please don't give false hope to Jun.
Please.
My apologies.
Seriously?
Wait.
Sorry, Tae-yeong.
I have an urgent meeting.
You haven't changed a bit.
Your apologies are never sincere.
You were always like that
when you snatched up the companies
I was in talks with first.
You knew how much I had invested
in those deals valued at billions,
trillions even.
But you just acted and apologized
like you bumped into me on the streets
or something.
"Sorry, Tae-yeong."
I'm glad that came across well.
You're right.
I wasn't really sorry.
Even if it weren't for me,
you could never have closed those deals.
Yeah?
People can instinctively tell
the difference between someone
who will help them grow
or devour them.
And you see,
you make it too obvious.
You have the look of a beast
standing over its prey.
Yeah, that's it.
Watch it.
Just one more thing before I do.
When it comes to elevators,
it's exit first
and enter after.
That's basic etiquette.
You should at least have basic manners.
Okay.
See you.
Hi.
What are you doing here again?
Back to interrogate me?
Why so cold? We're on the same team now.
What? Same team?
What's with the face?
It's nothing.
How's it going?
Well, I did as you said
and let Ji-hyeok handle
the new product development.
But what if it's successful?
Wouldn't that be bad for us?
Wait, was that Mr. Yu's idea?
We need to make sure that doesn't happen.
I thought you said we're on the same team.
Why did you tell her to do such a thing?
Stay out of his way and support him.
-Pardon?
-What?
This is our chance.
Our chance to use
that Go Da-rim card properly.
And don't worry.
Even if they produce something amazing,
it'll never see the light of day.
Instead of overthinking it
and obsessing over newness,
I thought we could find an older product
and give it an update.
We could each take one--
Who cares about our opinions?
We'll follow your lead on everything.
What?
You're the fountain of ideas on our team.
-That's right.
-You are.
Absolutely.
What are you talking about?
We always did everything together.
-First, we should divide the categories--
-You should tell her.
-But you're the oldest.
-Be quiet.
-You saw it.
-You saw it, so you speak up.
-No, you tell her.
-I don't even know if that's true.
Listen.
There's something…
I want to tell you.
I had a second to reflect
after my mom got discharged.
That's when I finally realized
that I did something unforgivable.
I'm deceiving those who trust me.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Stop that. It's fine. It's totally fine.
Sit down.
You should've told us sooner
if you were going through all that.
It's not like we wouldn't have understood.
I misunderstood you for no reason.
See? I told you
Da-rim wouldn't do something like that.
When the world has you standing
at the edge of a cliff,
you have to do whatever you can
to survive.
How could we not understand that?
That's right.
If it weren't for you,
we would've been cast aside like leftovers
before getting kicked out.
So don't cry.
You're all crying.
I'm only crying because you are.
But still, it doesn't change
the fact that I lied to get this job.
I'm going to leave after this project.
I already handed in my resignation.
Oh no.
I want to see
my Jin-hui,
Nan-suk,
and Go-eun
become full-time employees.
I'll consider this my last chance
to repay your kindness
and do my absolute best.
So…
let's do our best
until the very end, okay?
-Da-rim.
-I can't believe you.
I'm sorry.
Mr. Gong, we need to talk.
-About what?
-You'll see when we get there.
-Where are we going? Hold on.
-A restaurant.
I made a reservation at the most
expensive place near the office.
Let's go.
-Great.
-Let's go.
Let go of me.
Wait. Let me go. Let go!
Please let me go.
I said let go!
-Cheers.
I was so shocked
when I saw you two hugging each other.
I was really torn
about what to do about you two.
Mr. Kang, you're drinking more than usual.
How could I not?
Ji-hyeok betrayed me.
Hey, I didn't betray you.
I'm so disappointed in you.
You should've at least told me.
So you're saying
you had that banging dynamite kiss
with Ms. Go, right?
-"A banging dynamite kiss"?
Mr. Kang.
Are you drunk?
Hold on a second.
Didn't you tell us you two met
for the first time in Jeju?
And you shared an explosive,
dynamite kiss from the start?
Can you elaborate?
What exactly is a dynamite kiss?
How is it different from a regular kiss?
No, that's not…
-Well…
-Yes?
You explain it. I can't.
-So you see…
-Oh my goodness.
-It's like…
-Yeah?
I don't know what to say.
She can't say. She doesn't know.
Seriously? You two are so annoying.
I don't care
if it's an office affair or romance.
Let's just get rid of both of them.
I feel so empty inside, Nan-suk.
Eat as much as you want tonight.
It's on me.
Can we get more meat here?
A large, please!
Let's go hard tonight!
Congratulations.
Here's to your relationship.
-How nice.
-Is it good?
That must've been
really tough for you to do.
It was really brave of you to tell them.
I mean it.
I was really worried,
but they were all so understanding.
I feel bad about it…
and thankful at the same time.
Stop crying.
Okay?
It's okay.
I'm proud of you.
It's hot.
Be careful.
Thank you.
I should apologize to you as well.
Why?
For everything from when we met
until now.
You went through a lot emotionally
and suffered because of me.
That's true.
You're right about that.
It makes me very angry.
It does,
but all of it
is forgivable by the fact that…
you're single.
I think you're a really lucky person.
Thank you.
What's wrong with me?
Stop running away now.
I won't ever let you go.
So handsome.
I know.
What?
Why are you pretending to be asleep?
Because I'm happy.
Are we not going to get up?
We need to eat breakfast.
No thanks.
We need to wash our faces
and brush our teeth.
I don't want to.
Okay then. Let's just not do it.
You want to spend the whole day in bed?
Yeah.
And do what?
You know, just this and that.
This and that?
Yeah.
This and that…
Okay.
Hold on. Wait.
I guess Da-rim is sleeping in
because it's the weekend.
No.
She didn't come home last night.
She was drinking with a friend.
Maybe…
she has a boyfriend.
I wish.
She needs to start dating,
but she's not interested
because she's so ambitious
about her career.
Ji-hyeok is also so dedicated to his work.
It's always work and home for him.
I don't think
he's ever held a woman's hand before.
It's concerning, to say the least.
They say kids nowadays just don't date.
We should all be concerned.
By the way,
what kind of man does Da-rim like?
I wonder what she'd think of
someone like Ji-hyeok.
No, that can't happen.
Why not?
He's too handsome.
He's not handsome at all.
He's so average-looking.
Just walk through any street
and look around.
All guys look like him.
-Can you tell me where that street is?
-What?
I want to go and see.
Anyhow, it won't work.
They come from different worlds.
It's best to marry someone
with a similar background.
Eat up. The soup's getting cold.
This is delicious.
Sure.
She sure can drink like a fish.
I guess she gets that from me too.
Wake up. We're shopping
for your newlywed home today.
I don't care. I'm not going anywhere.
You go.
Why would I go alone?
-The sea sings
What's this?
So tell me.
Why were you at Mr. Kim's kid's
talent show?
Why did you go and sing?
Why else? I like him. That's why.
I told you I liked someone.
You crazy brat!
How could you be so immature?
Why him, out of all people?
-Have you lost your mind?
-What's wrong with him?
Pull yourself together!
Do you think marrying someone like Dad
is being mature?
Then I'm just going to be immature.
I refuse to live like you!
JUN BABY STUDIO
He's just some nameless photographer
and a single dad.
How dare he covet my daughter?
I let him hold an exhibition
in my art hall,
and this is how he repays me?
That ungrateful…
Damn it.
I'll get straight to the point.
Ha-yeong…
Are you okay?
That damn brat.
-Mr. Kim Seon-u.
-Just a second.
Can I see your wrist for a moment?
Excuse me.
Let's see.
It's a little cold.
Oh, you don't have to.
I also hurt my wrists a lot
because I spend all day
playing with children.
These pain relief patches are the best.
I'll put on one more.
It doesn't hurt, does it?
It should heal in no time.
Didn't you have something to say?
And this?
I didn't know what to get you.
I couldn't show up empty-handed, could I?
Thank you for this.
Grapefruits.
-Good.
-Okay, we'll get this.
What's your favorite pasta?
I'll make whatever you want.
You know how to cook pasta, Mr. Gong?
Of course, I do.
Wait.
We're on a date.
Can you stop calling me Mr. Gong?
Sorry, Mr. Gong.
Then what should I call you?
Ji-hyeok.
That's fine too, but…
Ba…
Baby? Like "baby boy"?
No, not that.
Babe.
Whatever, just forget it.
Babe, let's go!
Let's go, babe!
Come on, babe!
Ta-da!
This looks amazing!
Me?
Two.
Hold on.
You have something here.
No, not there.
Do you think marrying someone like Dad
is being mature?
Then I'm just going to be immature.
I refuse to live like you!
Water.
What?
What are you doing? Pour me some water.
Are you serious?
You can't even pour a cup of water?
I hurt my wrist.
You have another one!
That's true.
I forgot I had two arms.
Goddamn it.
This is the shortlist of products
we're looking to update.
Is the development team
working on any of them already?
We have nothing planned for them.
But the fact that we don't
means that those products already have
high customer satisfaction ratings.
An unnecessary update
could end up backfiring.
That's right. I know it's a challenge,
but I suggest you try
to come up with something
that's not already in our product line.
Then you'd also be pioneering
a new market for us.
That's true.
If I could offer a tip,
I'd say start recording everything
on your phone.
Record everything?
You don't know when an idea will strike.
Recording it the second you think of it
will be helpful.
Trial and error will be inevitable,
so if you record every step,
you'll be able to review
where it went wrong.
Oh, that makes sense.
Thank you.
-Thank you.
It looks uncomfortable.
So I think…
So I think it needs to be updated.
That's a must.
The size…
-I think diaper bags might be good.
-Diaper bags…
Look at this fabric.
Diapers?
That would be…
-Take a look at this one.
-This one too.
This one too.
This one's…
I'm not sure how it should be tied.
The way you tie it?
Let me do it.
This one? Or this one?
I think that one.
KNOT IS COMPLICATED AND DIFFICULT TO USE
UNCOMFORTABLE FOR BABY
NO POCKETS OR NOT ENOUGH FOR WIPES
HIP SEAT ADDS WEIGHT AND CAUSES STRAIN
THE WAY IT'S TIED
DETERMINES DIFFICULTY OF USE
Look. Next.
-Ta-da!
-That color is so nice.
-Yeah.
-It is.
This is nice.
-It's so pretty.
-It's good for a tone-on-tone look.
But I still think
the fabric is most important.
This isn't right.
How can I…
What's that?
Mr. Gong!
Seriously.
WITH BABY
-Ta-da!
Okay!
-This is excellent!
-We did it!
-Baby carrier.
-We did it.
Baby carrier.
To account for sweating in the summer,
we can use some sort of mesh fabric.
How about making it with mesh fabric
and detachable?
Two options for summer and winter.
You haven't texted me all day.
Here you are
just recording yourself again.
Are you going home, Mr. Gong?
No one's around.
Are you leaving already, babe?
I'll miss you so much through the night.
We can go home together.
To my place.
I can wait for you.
I really want to go with you,
but I still have a lot of work to do.
The prototype is coming out soon,
and we need to make final edits if needed.
You should go home.
I can't concentrate.
Hold on.
I left files in the meeting room.
Go first, okay?
See you tomorrow!
I'm going home first.
I'm really leaving.
I don't know why hearing you
tell me to go home makes me so sad.
Can't you stop me and make me stay?
I just want to
chat and laugh with you every day.
It's finally here.
-Hurry up and open it!
-I can't look at it.
-I'll open it for you.
-I can't.
-Oh my gosh, it's so pretty.
-It's so pretty.
-My goodness. I can't believe this.
-It looks so luxurious.
Oh my.
It's finally here.
Natural BeBe's first baby carrier.
That's right,
it's the baby carrier we created.
This is exactly how I felt
when I gave birth to my first son.
My goodness.
You know the feeling, right?
This will be out on the market
next week, right?
I'm not dreaming, am I?
Now, now.
You all worked really hard.
I'm sure we'll see positive results.
Mr. Gong!
Mr. Gong! You all need to look at this.
This came out so nicely.
Look at it.
This is the same as our prototype.
We never placed an order for this color.
This is a new product
that MomsJoy released this morning.
What?
That can't be. Why would our product
be released by another company?
Yeah, there must be some sort of mistake.
-Mr. Kang, you must be mistaken.
-No.
-Wait, hold on.
-What?
"MomsJoy is releasing a new baby carrier."
"It utilizes a body-hugging design
that notably reduces shoulder
and lower-back strain."
"It's made with cutting-edge materials
to make it lighter than a towel…"
It's the exact same materials
and features.
-That can't be.
-Are you being serious?
-Let me see.
-Are you serious?
They're so similar.
Who's Go Da-rim?
Chairman Gong.
I'm Go Da-rim.
You're Go Da-rim?
Oh my!
DYNAMITE KISS
So you knew she lied to get hired
and let it slide?
Yes.
But framing her for being a spy
when she didn't do anything?
That's enough.
He knew I lied and still covered for me,
and now he's in a tight spot.
You're just going to give up
on being promoted to vice president
and our joint venture with Taeyu C&T?
All because of a woman like her?
Think wisely!
I was the one who leaked the new product
to a competitor.
Why do you insist on suffering alone?
-Just trust me and--
-I'm suffering because of you.
Let's break up.
Let's each go back to where we belong.
This is me at rock bottom.
Subtitle translation by: Justin S. Kim